export const ReactQuestions = [
    // Question 1
    {
        question: "How many ways are there to define variables in ES6?",
        optionA: "one",
        optionB: "three",
        optionC: "four",
        optionD: "None of the above",
        answer: "optionB",
        isMultChoice: true,
    },
    // Question 2
    {
        question: "Which of the following is used to pass data to a component from outside in React?",
        optionA: "props",
        optionB: "passProp",
        optionC: "ES6",
        optionD: "propTypes",
        answer: "optionA",
        isMultChoice: true,
    },
    // Question 3
    {
        question: "React utilizes ___-way data binding to keep everything modular and fast",
        optionA: "two",
        optionB: "one",
        optionC: "four",
        optionD: "None of the above",
        answer: "optionB",
        isMultChoice: true,
    },
    // Question 4
    {
        question: " Which of the following keyword is used to create a class inheritance?",
        optionA: "inherits",
        optionB: "create",
        optionC: "this",
        optionD: "extends",
        answer: "optionD",
        isMultChoice: true,
    },
    // Question 5
    {
        question: "How many elements can a valid react component return?",
        optionA: "1",
        optionB: "2",
        optionC: "3",
        optionD: "4",
        answer: "optionA",
        isMultChoice: true,
    },
    // Question 6
    {
        question: "_____ are the building blocks of any React application.",
        optionA: "imports",
        optionB: "states",
        optionC: "components",
        optionD: "buttons",
        answer: "optionC",
        isMultChoice: true,
    },
    // Question 7
    {
        question: "True or false: React JS creates a virtual DOM in memory.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        answer: "optionA",
        isMultChoice: false,
    },
     // Question 8
     {
        question: "What are the two ways to handle data in React?",
        optionA: "state & services",
        optionB: "state & props",
        optionC: "components & jsx",
        optionD: "sql & jsx",
        answer: "optionB",
        isMultChoice: true,
    },
     // Question 9
     {
        question: " Which of the following method refers to the parent class in React.js?",
        optionA: "this()",
        optionB: "self()",
        optionC: "inherits()",
        optionD: "super()",
        answer: "optionD",
        isMultChoice: true,
    },
     // Question 10
     {
        question: "Which of the following best defines the \"key\" prop?",
        optionA: "used to gain access to styles in JSX",
        optionB: "A way for React to identify a newly added item in a list",
        optionC: "an HTML attribute",
        optionD: "A higher order array method",
        answer: "optionB",
        isMultChoice: true,
    },
     // Question 11
     {
        question: "How do you style components in React?",
        optionA: "Inline styling",
        optionB: "Javascript Object",
        optionC: "CSS stylesheet or framework",
        optionD: "All of the above",
        answer: "optionD",
        isMultChoice: true,
    },
     // Question 12
     {
        question: "True or false: React Router is a routing library used to create routes in a React application.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        answer: "optionA",
        isMultChoice: false,
    },
      // Question 13
      {
        question: "How do you update the state of a component?",
        optionA: "setState()",
        optionB: "useState()",
        optionC: "update()",
        optionD: "None of the above",
        answer: "optionA",
        isMultChoice: true,
    },

       // Question 14
       {
        question: "How does React increase performance in applications?",
        optionA: "By updating the DOM",
        optionB: "Through two-way data binding",
        optionC: "By updating the virtual DOM",
        optionD: "Through multi-threaded operations",
        answer: "optionC",
        isMultChoice: true,
    },
       // Question 15
       {
        question: "True or false: Web browsers can read JSX directly.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        answer: "optionB",
        isMultChoice: false,
    },

]




// React + .NET REST API

